mail@juriknauth.com | Fichtenweg 80, 13587 Berlin, Germany | 0049 17662329631 | juriknauth.com

Profile

I'm a game developer and I love what I do. I've been making games for about 6 years now. I've always had a passion for games, ever since I was a kid. And I knew that one day I wanted to develop them myself. There's something indescribably satisfying about seeing people experience the things you've created. Whether it's a player getting lost in an epic adventure or figuring out how to solve that one difficult puzzle, those "A-ha!" moments are what make all those long hours worth it.

EXPERIENCE

Beam cross realities, Berlin **Unity Developer** 2021 - Today Skills: Unity Development, AR, VR, Mobile, UI, Game Design ... Projects: Operation Legendary, Uvex Safety AR, Loop5 Arcades ... Lecturer, Freelance 2022 - Today Skills: Unity, Game Development, Game Art, Mentoring ... SAE, Berlin 2019 - 2020 Programming Teacher Assistant, Freelance Skills: Unity, Game Development, Game Design, Mentoring ... Pixelsplit, Frankfurt am Main 2018 **Unity Developer Intern** Skills: Unity Game Development, Game Design ... Projects: Deádly Days ... Phantom 8, Berlin Intern 2018 Skills: Unreal Engine, Quality Assurance, Game Design ... Projects: Past Cure Smilegate Europe, Berlin **Quality Assurance, Working Student** 2017 Skills: Quality Assurance Projects: CrossFire juriknauth, Berlin Solo Game Developer & Freelancer 2017 - Today

EDUCATION

Mediadesign Hochschule für Design und Informatik, Berlin Bachelor of Science, Game Design	2015 - 2019
Technische Universität, Berlin Transport Engineering	2012 - 2015
Freie Universität, Berlin History and Cultural Studies	2011 - 2012
Qantm College, Berlin Interactive Entertainment Design	2009 - 2011
Ecole européene Bruxelles II, Brussels European Baccalaureate, Art, Geography & Biology	1999 - 2009
ertificates/diplomes	

Game Development, Game Design, Game Art ...

Projects: Swear To God, Pirate Splashy, Ninja Car ...

CE

Mediadesign Hochschule für Design und Informatik, Berlin 3D Modelling Technique Specialization 2019 Mediadesign Hochschule für Design und Informatik, Berlin Classical Artwork 2019



SKILLS

Game Development	95%
Agile Development	90%
Unity	95%
C#	95%
Git	90%
Rapid-Prototyping	85%
Virtual Reality	90%
Augmented Rality	95%
Game Design	85%
UI/ UX Design	85%
Quality Assurance Web Development Game Art Project Management	80% 65% 75% 80%

LANGUAGES

German	Mother tongue
English	Fluent
Spanish	Basic
French	Basic

BERLIN, 2023-02-01

Venue, Date, Signature